[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":16653,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":65624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":17290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":82932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":7846,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":90808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":16311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":107131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1322,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":108459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":114712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2881,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":117596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":123913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2774,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":126692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is  6 or bi gger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":130265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":955,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":131223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4650,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":135879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":137044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2921,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":139970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1054,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":141027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to  perform  +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2684,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":143715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1034,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":144752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":147835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":918,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":148756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":151392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":964,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":152360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":6920,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":159296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similar ly, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":5411,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":164711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8328,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":173057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":178912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, th e invers e of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":6963,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":185881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":7345,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":193239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":201780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1251,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":203036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":208707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1445,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":210157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse  of 0 und er +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":213989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":841,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":214832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":2751,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":217589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":10003,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":227597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an eleme nt which  can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":233772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":9167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":242958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":247530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct ! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":3534,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":251071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":255887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</ sub>, be cause 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":30537,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":286436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":290467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1072,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":291551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questi ons abou t a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10499,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":302059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":307006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1094,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":308109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":310970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":315042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":317816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2605,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":320429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":323527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than 9 so it will just be 5","response_history":["4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than 9 so it will just be 5"],"rt":15619,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":339150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8 and 4 equal 12 which is higher than 9 so it will be 3","response_history":["8 and 4 equal 1 ","8 and 4 equal 12 which is higher than 9 so it will be 3"],"rt":11685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":350839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9 since it will get to 0","response_history":["9 since it will get to 0"],"rt":9722,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":360567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":366170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is  the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":7666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":373844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 since it gets 3 to 9","response_history":["6 since it gets 3 ti 0","6 since it gets 3 ti ","6 since it gets 3 ti","6 since it gets 3 to 9"],"rt":9424,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":383274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure","response_history":["I am not sure"],"rt":5530,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":388826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am honestly not sure","response_history":["yes since it","I am honestly not sure"],"rt":10566,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":399402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am forgetting how to get to the generator","response_history":["I am forgetting how to get to the generator"],"rt":9017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":408423,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how  you got  your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2579,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":411011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":8140,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":419155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":423382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I am not sure","response_history":["I","I am not sure"],"rt":8963,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":432348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Its just a number and it depends","response_history":["Its just a number and it deends on w","Its just a number and it deen","Its just a number and it dee","Its just a number and it depends"],"rt":14246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":446600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":451546,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":457895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":26082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":483986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"it has to be able to be divided into that number","response_history":["it has to be div","it has to be di","it has to be d","it has to be able to be divided into that number"],"rt":16038,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":500029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":87922,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":587960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"sometimes, it depends on other numbers","response_history":["sometime ","sometimesm ut","sometimesm u","sometimesm ","sometimesm","sometimes, it depends on other numbers"],"rt":13216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":601185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":[" Sometime s"],"rt":8846,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":610042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2626,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":612682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"30","response_history":["30"],"rt":72295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":684980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no  degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":60546,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":745536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"High school calculus","response_history":["Som fom ","High school calculus"],"rt":154850,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":900395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":904299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":907636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":5487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":913128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":915898,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":80840,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":996752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":999130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":180087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1179230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1182163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it was fun, I tried to understand as much as I could.","response_history":["it was  fun, I t rued","it was fun, I true","it was fun, I tru","it was fun, I trued to ","it was fun, I trued to","it was fun, I trued t","it was fun, I trued ","it was fun, I trued","it was fun, I true","it was fun, I tru","it was fun, I tried to unser","it was fun, I tried to unse","it was fun, I tried to uns","it was fun, I tried to understand as much as I could."],"rt":14852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1197024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]